Charles B. Gunn Collection 1988.0001
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series III: Photographs, undated, 1927-1985
  - Subseries A: Hurricanes, Floods and Derailments
    - Flood damage -- Falls Village, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 77.26 (1988-0001.ph414-ph423, UC19-0014), August 1955 (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - Flood damage -- Falls Village, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 77.86, over the Housatonic River (1988-0001.ph424-ph427), August 1955 (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - Flood damage -- North Canaan, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 81.49, over the Blackberry River (1988-0001.ph428-ph434, UC19-0015), August 1955 (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - Flood damage -- North Canaan, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph435), August 1955 (Box 7, Folder 122)
    - Flood damage -- North of Sheffield, Massachusetts, repair of Bridge 88.23 (1988-0001.ph436-ph439), August 1955 (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - Flood damage -- Derby Junction, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 8.69 (1988-0001.ph440-ph452, UC19-0016), August 1955 (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Flood damage -- Derby Junction, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 8.69 (1988-0001.ph453-ph465), August 1955 (Box 8, Folder 125)
    - Flood damage -- Derby Junction, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 8.69 (1988-0001.ph466-ph473), August 1955 (Box 8, Folder 126)
    - Flood damage -- Derby Junction, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 8.69 (1988-0001.ph474-ph478), August 1955 (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - Flood damage -- Derby, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph479-ph486, UC19-0017), August 1955 (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Flood damage -- Naugatuck River south of Ansonia, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 10.25 (1988-0001.ph487-ph497), August 1955 (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - Flood damage -- Naugatuck River south of Ansonia, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 10.25 (1988-0001.ph498-ph503), August 1955 (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - Flood damage -- Ansonia, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph504-ph509, UC19-0018, UC19-0019), August 1955 (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - Flood damage -- Naugatuck River north of Ansonia, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 12.51 (1988-0001.ph510-ph515), August 1955 (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - Flood damage -- Naugatuck River at Seymour, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 14.59 (1988-0001.ph516-ph527, UC19-0020), August 1955 (Box 9, Folder 133)
    - Flood damage -- Naugatuck River at Seymour, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 14.59 (1988-0001.ph528-ph537), August 1955 (Box 9, Folder 134)
    - Flood damage -- Naugatuck River at Seymour, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 14.59 (1988-0001.ph538-ph548), August 1955 (Box 9, Object 135)
    - Flood damage -- Beacon Falls, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph549-ph554), August 1955 (Box 9, Folder 136)
    - Flood damage -- Beacon Falls, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph555-ph560), August 1955 (Box 9, Folder 137)
    - Flood damage -- Naugatuck, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph561-ph568, UC19-0021), August 1955 (Box 9, Folder 138)
    - Flood damage -- Naugatuck, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph569-ph576), August 1955 (Box 9, Folder 139)
    - Flood damage -- Naugatuck, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph577-ph581), August 1955 (Box 9, Folder 140)
    - Flood damage -- Waterbury, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph582-ph591, UC19-0023), August 1955 (Box 10, Folder 141)
    - Flood damage -- Waterbury, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph31, 1988-0001.ph592-ph598, 1988-0001.ph600-ph605), August 1955 (Box 10, Folder 142)
    - Flood damage -- Scovill sidetrack at Waterbury, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 18.93 (1988-0001.ph606-ph609), August 1955 (Box 10, Folder 143)
    - Flood damage -- Scovill sidetrack east of Naugatuck River at Waterbury, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 19.27 (1988-0001.ph610-ph618,UC19-0024), August 1955 (Box 10, Folder 144)
    - Flood damage -- Jackson Street in Waterbury, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 63.06 (1988-0001.ph619-ph628, UC19-0025), August 1955 (Box 10, Folder 145)
    - Flood damage -- Jackson Street in Waterbury, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 63.06 (1988-0001.ph629-ph635, UC19-0026), August 1955 (Box 10, Folder 146)
    - Flood damage -- Waterbury, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 63.14 over Naugatuck River (1988-0001.ph636-ph644, UC19-0027), August 1955 (Box 10, Folder 147)
    - Flood damage -- Waterbury, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 63.14 over Naugatuck River (1988-0001.ph645-ph653, UC19-0028), August 1955 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - Flood damage -- Bank Street in Waterbury, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 63.21 over Naugatuck River (1988-0001.ph654), August 1955 (Box 11, Folder 149)
    - Flood damage -- Washington Avenue west of Waterbury, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 63.36 (1988-0001.ph655-ph660, UC19-0029), August 1955 (Box 11, Folder 150)
    - Flood damage -- Washington Avenue west of Waterbury, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 63.36 (1988-0001.ph661-ph665), August 1955 (Box 11, Folder 151)
    - Flood damage -- Liberty Street in Waterbury, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph666-ph667), August 1955 (Box 11, Folder 152)
    - Flood damage -- Watertown branch in Waterbury, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph668-ph671), August 1955 (Box 11, Folder 153)
    - Flood damage -- Oakville, Connecticut, aerial view (UC19-0030), August 1955 (Box 11, Folder 154)
    - Flood damage -- Huntington Street south of Waterville, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 29.31 (1988-0001.ph672-ph681), August 1955 (Box 11, Folder 155)
    - Flood damage -- North of Waterville, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 30.64 over Naugatuck River (1988-0001.ph682-ph691), August 1955 (Box 11, Folder 156)
    - Flood damage -- Three miles north of Waterville, Connecticut, towards Thomaston, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 32.89 over Naugatuck River (1988-0001.ph692-ph704), August 1955 (Box 11, Folder 157)
    - Flood damage -- Three miles north of Waterville, Connecticut, towards Thomaston, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 32.89 over Naugatuck River (1988-0001.ph705-ph715), August 1955 (Box 11, Folder 158)
    - Flood damage -- Thomaston, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph716-ph725), August 1955 (Box 12, Folder 159)
    - Flood damage -- South of East Litchfield, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 42.52 over Baldwin's Brook (1988-0001.ph726-ph729), August 1955 (Box 12, Folder 160)
    - Flood damage -- Torrington, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph730-ph739), August 1955 (Box 12, Folder 161)
    - Flood damage -- Winsted, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph740-ph754), August 1955 (Box 12, Folder 162)
    - Flood damage -- Winsted, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph755-ph781), August 1955 (Box 12, Folder 163)
    - Flood damage -- Terryville, Connecticut; Bristol, Connecticut; and Plainville, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph782-ph785), August 1955 (Box 12, Folder 164)
    - Flood damage -- Plainville, Connecticut, aerial views (1988-0001.ph786-ph790), August 1955 (Box 12, Folder 165)
    - Flood damage -- Farmington, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph791-ph801), August 1955 (Box 13, Folder 166)
    - Flood damage -- Farmington, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 32.00 over Farmington River (1988-0001.ph802-ph814), August 1955 (Box 13, Folder 167)
    - Flood damage -- Farmington, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 32.00 over Farmington River (1988-0001.ph815-ph827), August 1955 (Box 13, Folder 168)
    - Flood damage -- North of Farmington, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 32.25 over Connecticut Route 4 (1988-0001.ph830-ph844), August 1955 (Box 13, Folder 169)
    - Flood damage -- Unionville, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph845-ph847), August 1955 (Box 13, Folder 170)
    - Flood damage -- Collinsville, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph848-ph856), August 1955 (Box 13, Folder 171)
    - Flood damage -- New Hartford, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph857), August 1955 (Box 13, Folder 172)
    - Flood damage -- Avon, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph858-ph860), August 1955 (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Flood damage -- Simsbury, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph861-ph863), August 1955 (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Flood damage -- Granby, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph864-ph865), August 1955 (Box 13, Folder 175)
    - Flood damage -- Granby, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 46.44 over Salmon Brook (1988-0001.ph866-ph872), August 1955 (Box 13, Folder 176)
    - Flood damage -- Westfield, Massachusetts, at Powder Mill and Sacket Brook Culvert (1988-0001.ph873-ph879), August 1955 (Box 13, Folder 177)
    - Flood damage -- Westfield, Massachusetts, repair of Bridge 58.72 at Ponder's Hollow Road (1988-0001.ph880-ph889), August 1955 (Box 14, Folder 178)
    - Flood damage -- Easthampton, Massachusetts, repair of Bridge 68.81 (1988-0001.ph890-ph894), August 1955 (Box 14, Folder 179)
    - Flood damage -- 1.24 miles north of Easthampton, Massachusetts, repair of Bridge 72.64 (1988-0001.ph895-ph902), August 1955 (Box 14, Folder 180)
    - Flood damage -- Rocky Hill, Connecticut; and Cromwell, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph903-ph904), August 1955 (Box 14, Folder 181)
    - Flood damage -- Hartford, Connecticut, and Camp Courant in West Hartford, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph905-ph910), August 1955 (Box 14, Folder 182)
    - Flood damage -- Windsor Locks, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph911-ph916), August 1955 (Box 14, Folder 183)
    - Flood damage -- Stafford Springs, Connecticut, and south of Norwich, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph917-ph920), August 1955 (Box 14, Folder 184)
    - Flood damage -- North of Putnam, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 61.31 over Quinebaug River (1988-0001.ph921-ph929), August 1955 (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Flood damage -- Putnam, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph930-ph941), August 1955 (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Flood damage -- Putnam, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph942-ph952), August 1955 (Box 15, Folder 187)
    - Flood damage -- Putnam, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph953-ph964), August 1955 (Box 15, Folder 188)
    - Flood damage -- Putnam, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 45.47 over Providence Street at railroad yard (1988-0001.ph965-ph976), August 1955 (Box 15, Folder 189)
    - Flood damage -- North of Grosvenordale in Thompson, Connecticut, Bridge 49.47 over French River (1988-0001.ph977-ph990), August 1955 (Box 15, Folder 190)
    - Flood damage -- Grosvenordale and North Grosvenordale in Thompson, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph991-ph1005), August 1955 (Box 15, Folder 191)
    - Flood damage -- North of Wilsonville in Thompson, Connecticut, Bridge 52.94 over French River (1988-0001.ph1006-ph1009), August 1955 (Box 15, Folder 192)
    - Flood damage -- Webster, Massachusetts (1988-0001.ph1010-ph1013), August 1955 (Box 16, Folder 193)
    - Flood damage -- Webster, Massachusetts, Bridge 55.96 (1988-0001.ph1014-ph1019), August 1955 (Box 16, Folder 194)
    - Flood damage -- Webster, Massachusetts, Bridge 5.75 (1988-0001.ph1020-ph1024), August 1955 (Box 16, Folder 195)
    - Flood damage -- Dudley, Massachusetts, Bridge 6.58 (1988-0001.ph1025-ph1028), August 1955 (Box 16, Folder 196)
    - Flood damage -- West Dudley, Massachusetts, Bridge 13.49 over Quinebaug River (1988-0001.ph1029-ph1041), August 1955 (Box 16, Folder 197)
    - Flood damage -- Worcester, Massachusetts, Bridge 68.92, North Hope Avenue (1988-0001.ph1042-ph1045), August 1955 (Box 16, Folder 198)
    - Flood damage -- Millbury, Massachusetts, Bridge 37.74 (1988-0001.ph1046-ph1048), August 1955 (Box 16, Folder 199)
    - Flood damage -- South of Albion, Rhode Island, Bridge 10.56 over Blackstone River (1988-0001.ph1049-ph1060), August 1955 (Box 17, Folder 200)
    - Flood damage -- West of Woonsocket, Rhode Island, Bridge 29.18 over Blackstone River (1988-0001.ph1061-ph1062), August 1955 (Box 17, Folder 201)
    - Flood damage -- Woonsocket, Rhode Island (1988-0001.ph1063-ph1069), August 1955 (Box 17, Folder 202)
    - Flood damage -- Woonsocket Junction, Rhode Island, Bridge 34.36 over culvert (1988-0001.ph1070-ph1076), August 1955 (Box 17, Folder 203)
    - Flood damage -- Blackstone, Massachusetts, including the Bridge Street bridge (1988-0001.ph1077-ph1079), August 1955 (Box 17, Folder 204)
    - Flood damage -- Blackstone, Massachusetts, over Blackstone River (1988-0001.ph1080-ph1085), August 1955 (Box 17, Folder 205)
    - Flood damage -- Naugutuck Valley in Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1086-ph1095), August 1955 (Box 17, Folder 206)
    - Flood damage -- unknown locations (1988-0001.ph1096-ph1102), August 1955 (Box 17, Folder 207)
    - Large mounted photographs of scenes of flood damage (1988-0001.ph1593-ph1601), August 1955 (Box 22, Folder 255)
    - Derailment -- North of Sheffield, Massachusetts, at Bridge 88.43 (1988-0001.ph1103-ph1112), September 1955 (Box 17, Folder 208)
    - Derailment -- North of Sheffield, Massachusetts, at Bridge 88.43 (1988-0001.ph1113-ph1125), September 1955 (Box 17, Folder 209)
    - Derailment -- Sagamore, Massachusetts, at Bridge 88.43 (1988-0001.ph1126-ph1130), September 14, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 210)
    - Flood damage -- Glenbrook, Connecticut, washout of mainline (1988-0001.ph1573-ph1582), October 1955 (Box 18, Folder 211)
    - Flood damage -- Glenbrook, Connecticut, washout of mainline (1988-0001.ph1583-ph1592), October 1955 (Box 18, Folder 212)
    - Flood damage -- Springdale, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1133-ph1138), October 1955 (Box 18, Folder 213)
    - Flood damage -- Norwalk, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1139-ph1154), October 1955 (Box 18, Folder 214)
    - Flood damage -- Norwalk, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1155-ph1165), October 1955 (Box 18, Folder 215)
    - Flood damage -- Wilton, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1166-ph1175), October 1955 (Box 18, Folder 216)
    - Flood damage -- Cannondale, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1176-ph1190), October 1955 (Box 18, Folder 217)
    - Flood damage -- Cannondale, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1607-ph1617), October 1955 (Box 24, Folder 259)
    - Flood damage -- between Georgetown and Branchville, Connecticut, Bridge 14.92 (1988-0001.ph1191-ph1195), October 1955 (Box 18, Folder 218)
    - Flood damage -- Branchville, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1196-ph1197), October 1955 (Box 19, Folder 219)
    - Flood damage -- Dam at North Grosvenerdale, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1660-ph1687), October 1955 (Box 24, Folder 266)
    - Flood damage -- Redding, Connecticut, Bridge 19.84 (1988-0001.ph1198-ph1199), October 1955 (Box 19, Folder 220)
    - Flood damage -- Danbury, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1200-ph1203), October 1955 (Box 19, Folder 221)
    - Flood damage and derailment at Darien, Connecticut, anchor bridge 453 (1988-0001.ph1204-ph1216), October 1955 (Box 19, Folder 222)
    - Flood damage -- Dam at Webster, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1691-ph1693), October 1955 (Box 24, Folder 268)
    - Flood damage -- Dam at Wilsonville, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1688-ph1690), October 1955 (Box 24, Folder 267)
    - Flood damage -- Wilton, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1618-ph1627), October 1955 (Box 24, Folder 260)
    - Flood damage -- West Dudley, Massachusetts (1988-0001.ph2001-ph2002), October 1955 (Box 25, Folder 304)
    - Flood damage -- Albion, Rhode Island (1988-0001.ph1647-ph1650), undated (Box 24, Folder 263)
    - Flood damage -- Woonsocket, Rhode Island (1988-0001.ph1651-ph1658), undated (Box 24, Folder 264)
    - Derailment -- South Norwalk, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1217-ph1225), November 26, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 223)
    - Washout at Stone Arch Culvert in Glenbrook, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1226-ph1238), December 1955 (Box 19, Folder 224)
    - Grade crossing accident in North Haven, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1239-ph1248), January 20, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 225)
    - Wind and water damage to unidentified railroad structures (1988-0001.ph1249-ph1260), [mid-1950s] (Box 16, Folder 226)
  - Subseries B: Railroad stations and structures
    - Bridges -- Poughkeepsie, New York (1988-0001.ph1638-ph1646), May 1955 (Box 24, Folder 262)
    - Bridges -- Queens, New York -- Hell Gate Bridge (1988-0001.ph1628-ph1637), May 1955 (Box 24, Folder 261)
    - Freight house -- Willimantic, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1261), 1954 (Box 20, Folder 227)
    - Terminal facilities -- New Haven, Connecticut, (1988-0001.ph1262-ph1265), 1954 (Box 20, Folder 228)
    - Station development -- New Haven, Connecticut, aerial views (1988-0001.ph1266-ph1276, ph2166-2167), 1960s (Box 20, Folder 299)
    - Station rededication -- New Haven, Connecticut, (1988-0001.ph1277-ph1288), July 1985 (Box 20, Folder 230)
    - Stations -- Bethel, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1708-ph1710, 1988-0001.ph2125), September 1954 (Box 24, Folder 271)
    - Stations -- Branchville, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1711-ph1715, 1988-0001.ph2126), October 1954 (Box 24, Folder 272)
    - Stations -- Branford, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1716-ph1722, 1988-0001.ph2127), July 1954 (Box 24, Folder 273)
    - Stations -- Canaan, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1723-ph1725, 1988-0001.ph2155-2159), June 1955 (Box 24, Folder 274)
    - Stations -- Cos Cob, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1726-ph1734, 1988-0001.ph2160), August 1954-July 1955 (Box 24, Folder 275)
    - Stations -- Darien, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1735-ph1737, 1988-0001.ph2128), August 1954 (Box 24, Folder 276)
    - Stations -- East Norwalk, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1738-ph1748, 1988-0001.ph2129), June 1955 (Box 24, Folder 277)
    - Stations -- Fairfield, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1749-ph1755, 1988-0001.ph2130), August 1954 (Box 24, Folder 278)
    - Stations -- Greenwich, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1756-ph1765, 1988-0001.ph2131, 1988-0001.ph2161), August 1954-July 1955 (Box 24, Folder 279)
    - Stations -- Kent, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1766-ph1777, 1988-0001.ph2132), May 1955 (Box 24, Folder 280)
    - Stations and Railway Express Building -- New Haven, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1778-ph1789, 1988-0001.ph2162), May 1955 (Box 24, Folder 281)
    - Stations -- New London, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1790-ph1794, 19, 1988-0001.ph2163), April 1955 (Box 24, Folder 282)
    - Stations -- New London, Connecticut, model and designs for proposed station (1988-0001.ph1795-ph1799), undated (Box 24, Folder 283)
    - Stations -- New Milford, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1800-ph1815), May 1955 (Box 24, Folder 284)
    - Stations -- Noroton Heights, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1816-ph1817), September 1955 (Box 24, Folder 285)
    - Stations -- Norwalk, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1818-ph1837), September 1954-October 1955 (Box 24, Folder 286)
    - Stations -- Riverside, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1838-ph1846, 1988-0001.ph2164), August 1954-July 1955 (Box 24, Folder 287)
    - Stations -- Rowayton, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1847-ph1859), September 1954-February 1955 (Box 25, Folder 288)
    - Stations -- Springdale, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1860-ph1867), May 1955, undated (Box 25, Folder 289)
    - Stations -- Stamford, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1868-ph1883, 1988-0001.ph2133-ph2134, 1988-0001.ph2165), May 1955 (Box 25, Folder 290)
    - Stations -- Stratford, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1884-ph1889, 1988-0001.ph2135), September 1954 (Box 25, Folder 291)
    - Stations -- Torrington, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1890-ph1901, 1988-0001.ph2136-ph2137), September 1955 (Box 25, Folder 292)
    - Stations -- Westport, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1902-ph1918, 1988-0001.ph2138), May-August 1955 (Box 25, Folder 293)
    - Stations -- Buzzard's Bay, Massachusetts (1988-0001.ph1964-ph1973, 1988-0001.ph2147-2148), June 1955 (Box 25, Folder 300)
    - Stations -- East Walpole, Massachusetts (1988-0001.ph1974-ph1987), October 1955 (Box 25, Folder 301)
    - Stations -- Egypt, Massachusetts (1988-0001.ph1919-ph1927, 1988-0001.ph2139), July 1955 (Box 25, Folder 294)
    - Stations -- Falmouth, Massachusetts (1988-0001.ph1928-ph1946, 1988-0001.ph2140), May 1955 (Box 25, Folder 295)
    - Stations -- North Falmouth, Massachusetts (1988-0001.ph1947-ph1951, 1988-0001.ph2141), June 1955 (Box 25, Folder 296)
    - Stations -- Route 128 station in Massachusetts (1988-0001.ph1952-ph1956, 1988-0001.ph2142-ph2144), June 1955 (Box 25, Folder 297)
    - Stations -- Sandwich, Massachusetts (1988-0001.ph1957-ph1960, 1988-0001.ph2145-ph2146), June 1955 (Box 25, Folder 298)
    - Stations -- Sheffield, Massachusetts (1988-0001.ph1988-ph1993, 1988-0001.ph2149), June 1955 (Box 25, Folder 302)
    - Stations -- Springfield, Massachusetts (1988-0001.ph1961-ph1963), December 1954 (Box 25, Folder 299)
    - Stations -- West Barnstable, Massachusetts (1988-0001.ph1994-ph2000, 1988-0001.ph2150), June 1955 (Box 25, Folder 303)
    - Stations -- Wood's Hole, Massachusetts (1988-0001.ph2003-ph2009, 1988-0001.ph2151), June 1955 (Box 25, Folder 305)
    - Stations -- Harrison, New York (1988-0001.ph2010-ph2015), August 1955 (Box 25, Folder 306)
    - Stations -- Mamaroneck, New York (1988-0001.ph2016-ph2017), July 1955 (Box 25, Folder 307)
    - Stations -- New Rochelle, New York (1988-0001.ph2018-ph2030), June 1955 (Box 25, Folder 308)
    - Stations -- Pelham, New York (1988-0001.ph2031-ph2041), August 1954-June 1955 (Box 25, Folder 309)
    - Stations -- Rye, New York (1988-0001.ph2042-ph2047), August 1954 (Box 25, Folder 310)
    - Stations -- Kingston, Rhode Island (1988-0001.ph2048-ph2071, 1988-0001.ph2152), undated (Box 25, Folder 311)
    - Stations -- Pontiac, Rhode Island (1988-0001.ph2072-ph2078, 1988-0001.ph2153), August 1955 (Box 25, Folder 312)
    - Stations -- Providence, Rhode Island (1988-0001.ph2079-ph2086), November 1954 (Box 25, Folder 313)
    - Stations -- Wickford Junction, Rhode Island (1988-0001.ph2087-ph2099, 1988-0001.ph2154), undated (Box 25, Folder 314)
    - Highway bridge, construction of, over railroad tracks in New Haven, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1289-ph1304), August 1959 (Box 20, Folder 231)
    - Highway bridge, construction of, over railroad tracks in New Haven, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1305-ph1319), August 1959 (Box 20, Folder 232)
    - Highway bridge, construction of, over railroad tracks in New Haven, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1320-ph1334), August 1959 (Box 20, Folder 233)
    - Highway bridge, construction of, over railroad tracks in New Haven, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph1335-ph1348), August 1959 (Box 20, Folder 234)
  - Subseries C: Other subjects
    - Advertising for the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company (1988-0001.ph1349), [1940s] (Box 20, Folder 235)
    - Broken rail of an unidentified line (1988-0001.ph1350-ph1353), undated (Box 20, Folder 236)
    - Ceremonies -- Welded Rail Process Ceremony, Montowese, Connecticut, (Patrick McGinnis in photograph) (1988-0001.ph1659), July 1955 (Box 24, Folder 265)
    - Equipment (1988-0001.ph1694-ph1696), May 1955 (Box 24, Folder 269)
    - Fire on tracks in unidentified location along Shoreline route (1988-0001.ph1354-ph1355), undated (Box 20, Folder 237)
    - Locomotives and rolling stock (1988-0001.ph1356-ph1372), 1950s-1980s,undated (Box 21, Folder 238)
    - Marine equipment (1988-0001.ph1373-ph1375), 1953, undated (Box 21, Folder 239)
    - People -- George Alpert (1988-0001.ph1376-ph1387), [1950s] (Box 21, Folder 240)
    - People -- William S. Carr, General Superintendent and later assistant to the General Manager of the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company who was Director General of the military railroads in Korea from August 1950 to March 1951, (1988-0001.ph1388-ph1396), [1950s] (Box 21, Folder 241)
    - People -- Fidel Castro at the New Haven, Connecticut, railroad station (1988-0001.ph1397-ph1409), 1959 (Box 21, Folder 242)
    - People -- Fidel Castro at the New Haven, Connecticut, railroad station (1988-0001.ph1602-ph1603), 1959 (Box 22, Folder 256)
    - People -- Harry C. Dorrigan, Richard Joyce Smith, and an unidentified man, trustees of the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company (1988-0001.ph1604), [1960s] (Box 22, Folder 257)
    - People -- Charles B. Gunn (1988-0001.ph1410-ph1412), 1955, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 243)
    - People -- Patrick B. McGinnis (1988-0001.ph1413-ph1423), 1954 (Box 21, Folder 244)
    - People -- H.T. Moorhead, Assistant General Passenger Traffic Manager, Boston, in the 1950s, and later Assistant Vice President Passenger Traffic, New Haven, (1988-0001.ph1424-ph1427), 1955 (Box 21, Folder 245)
    - People -- J.V. Whalen, General Passenger Agent, Boston, (1988-0001.ph1428-ph1430), undated (Box 21, Folder 246)